[
  {
    "question": "戦",
    "answer": "いくさ"
  },
  {
    "question": "雷",
    "answer": "かみなり"
  },
  {
    "question": "日没",
    "answer": "にちぼつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "哀愁",
    "answer": "あいしゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "相撲",
    "answer": "すもう"
  },
  {
    "question": "寛容",
    "answer": "かんよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "脊椎",
    "answer": "せきつい"
  },
  {
    "question": "鶴見",
    "answer": "つるみ"
  },
  {
    "question": "慶事",
    "answer": "けいじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "合掌",
    "answer": "がっしょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "胴体",
    "answer": "どうたい"
  },
  {
    "question": "笑顔",
    "answer": "えがお"
  },
  {
    "question": "酪農",
    "answer": "らくのう"
  },
  {
    "question": "弓道",
    "answer": "きゅうどう"
  },
  {
    "question": "縫う",
    "answer": "ぬう"
  },
  {
    "question": "弔電",
    "answer": "ちょうでん"
  },
  {
    "question": "挑戦",
    "answer": "ちょうせん"
  },
  {
    "question": "賢い",
    "answer": "かしこい"
  },
  {
    "question": "梅雨",
    "answer": "つゆ"
  },
  {
    "question": "鎌",
    "answer": "かま"
  },
  {
    "question": "後れる",
    "answer": "おくれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "一騎当千",
    "answer": "いっきとうせん"
  },
  {
    "question": "弔う",
    "answer": "とむらう"
  },
  {
    "question": "概観",
    "answer": "がいかん"
  },
  {
    "question": "木棺",
    "answer": "もっかん"
  },
  {
    "question": "五月雨",
    "answer": "さみだれ"
  },
  {
    "question": "穂",
    "answer": "ほ"
  },
  {
    "question": "弟子",
    "answer": "でし"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄化粧",
    "answer": "うすげしょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "彫る",
    "answer": "ほる"
  },
  {
    "question": "悔恨",
    "answer": "かいこん"
  },
  {
    "question": "郷愁",
    "answer": "きょうしゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "五月",
    "answer": "さつき"
  },
  {
    "question": "刈る",
    "answer": "かる"
  },
  {
    "question": "授かる",
    "answer": "さずかる"
  },
  {
    "question": "美麗",
    "answer": "びれい"
  },
  {
    "question": "遷都",
    "answer": "せんと"
  },
  {
    "question": "葛藤",
    "answer": "かっとう"
  },
  {
    "question": "謙遜",
    "answer": "けんそん"
  },
  {
    "question": "時雨",
    "answer": "しぐれ"
  },
  {
    "question": "釜飯",
    "answer": "かまめし"
  },
  {
    "question": "程",
    "answer": "ほど"
  },
  {
    "question": "悔やむ",
    "answer": "くやむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "匿名",
    "answer": "とくめい"
  },
  {
    "question": "核心",
    "answer": "かくしん"
  },
  {
    "question": "双方",
    "answer": "そうほう"
  },
  {
    "question": "風邪",
    "answer": "かぜ"
  },
  {
    "question": "脚",
    "answer": "あし"
  },
  {
    "question": "神業",
    "answer": "かみわざ"
  },
  {
    "question": "袖",
    "answer": "そで"
  },
  {
    "question": "免責",
    "answer": "めんせき"
  },
  {
    "question": "制御",
    "answer": "せいぎょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "伯仲",
    "answer": "はくちゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "日和",
    "answer": "ひより"
  },
  {
    "question": "検索",
    "answer": "けんさく"
  },
  {
    "question": "得る",
    "answer": "うる"
  },
  {
    "question": "袋",
    "answer": "ふくろ"
  },
  {
    "question": "失踪",
    "answer": "しっそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "御礼",
    "answer": "おんれい"
  },
  {
    "question": "吉報",
    "answer": "きっぽう"
  },
  {
    "question": "心地",
    "answer": "ここち"
  },
  {
    "question": "寛大",
    "answer": "かんだい"
  },
  {
    "question": "酢酸",
    "answer": "さくさん"
  },
  {
    "question": "敷居",
    "answer": "しきい"
  },
  {
    "question": "詐称",
    "answer": "さしょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "挑む",
    "answer": "いどむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "文壇",
    "answer": "ぶんだん"
  },
  {
    "question": "土産",
    "answer": "みやげ"
  },
  {
    "question": "鎌倉",
    "answer": "かまくら"
  },
  {
    "question": "煮物",
    "answer": "にもの"
  },
  {
    "question": "裁縫",
    "answer": "さいほう"
  },
  {
    "question": "砂浜",
    "answer": "すなはま"
  },
  {
    "question": "恨む",
    "answer": "うらむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "老婆心",
    "answer": "ろうばしん"
  },
  {
    "question": "謙虚",
    "answer": "けんきょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "穂先",
    "answer": "ほさき"
  },
  {
    "question": "石臼",
    "answer": "いしうす"
  },
  {
    "question": "華麗",
    "answer": "かれい"
  },
  {
    "question": "俊足",
    "answer": "しゅんそく"
  },
  {
    "question": "藤",
    "answer": "ふじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "後輩",
    "answer": "こうはい"
  },
  {
    "question": "双子",
    "answer": "ふたご"
  },
  {
    "question": "酢",
    "answer": "す"
  },
  {
    "question": "詰まる",
    "answer": "つまる"
  },
  {
    "question": "後悔",
    "answer": "こうかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼻孔",
    "answer": "びこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "叔母",
    "answer": "おば"
  },
  {
    "question": "侍",
    "answer": "さむらい"
  },
  {
    "question": "吉日",
    "answer": "きちじつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "煮込む",
    "answer": "にこむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "完膚",
    "answer": "かんぷ"
  },
  {
    "question": "悔しい",
    "answer": "くやしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛嬢",
    "answer": "あいじょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "海峡",
    "answer": "かいきょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "一遍",
    "answer": "いっぺん"
  },
  {
    "question": "侍医",
    "answer": "じい"
  },
  {
    "question": "臼歯",
    "answer": "きゅうし"
  },
  {
    "question": "繁茂",
    "answer": "はんも"
  },
  {
    "question": "雷鳴",
    "answer": "らいめい"
  },
  {
    "question": "変遷",
    "answer": "へんせん"
  },
  {
    "question": "胴衣",
    "answer": "どうい"
  },
  {
    "question": "仮名",
    "answer": "がな"
  },
  {
    "question": "普遍的",
    "answer": "ふへんてき"
  },
  {
    "question": "詰める",
    "answer": "つめる"
  },
  {
    "question": "妖精",
    "answer": "ようせい"
  },
  {
    "question": "凹凸",
    "answer": "おうとつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "免許",
    "answer": "めんきょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "賢明",
    "answer": "けんめい"
  },
  {
    "question": "三味線",
    "answer": "しゃみせん"
  },
  {
    "question": "車椅子",
    "answer": "くるまいす"
  },
  {
    "question": "充填",
    "answer": "じゅうてん"
  },
  {
    "question": "小柄",
    "answer": "こがら"
  },
  {
    "question": "慶弔",
    "answer": "けいちょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "詐取",
    "answer": "さしゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "進捗",
    "answer": "しんちょく"
  },
  {
    "question": "足袋",
    "answer": "たび"
  },
  {
    "question": "三脚",
    "answer": "さんきゃく"
  },
  {
    "question": "結膜",
    "answer": "けつまく"
  },
  {
    "question": "膝",
    "answer": "ひざ"
  },
  {
    "question": "彫刻",
    "answer": "ちょうこく"
  },
  {
    "question": "海浜",
    "answer": "かいひん"
  },
  {
    "question": "冥福",
    "answer": "めいふく"
  },
  {
    "question": "草履",
    "answer": "ぞうり"
  },
  {
    "question": "探索",
    "answer": "たんさく"
  },
  {
    "question": "皮膚",
    "answer": "ひふ"
  },
  {
    "question": "手提げ",
    "answer": "てさげ"
  },
  {
    "question": "妊娠",
    "answer": "にんしん"
  },
  {
    "question": "令嬢",
    "answer": "れいじょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "出棺",
    "answer": "しゅっかん"
  },
  {
    "question": "太刀",
    "answer": "たち"
  },
  {
    "question": "威嚇",
    "answer": "いかく"
  },
  {
    "question": "処方箋",
    "answer": "しょほうせん"
  },
  {
    "question": "瞳",
    "answer": "ひとみ"
  },
  {
    "question": "搭乗",
    "answer": "とうじょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "御飯",
    "answer": "ごはん"
  },
  {
    "question": "老翁",
    "answer": "ろうおう"
  },
  {
    "question": "竹刀",
    "answer": "しない"
  },
  {
    "question": "羞恥心",
    "answer": "しゅうちしん"
  },
  {
    "question": "解剖",
    "answer": "かいぼう"
  },
  {
    "question": "娘",
    "answer": "むすめ"
  }
]
